export default [
  {
    question: 'What is 2 + 2?',
    options: ['3', '4', '5', '6'],
    correctOptions: [1],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 5 * 3?',
    options: ['10', '12', '15', '18'],
    correctOptions: [2],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 10 - 7?',
    options: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    correctOptions: [2],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 8 / 4?',
    options: ['2', '3', '4', '5'],
    correctOptions: [0],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 3 + 7?',
    options: ['9', '10', '11', '12'],
    correctOptions: [1],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are even numbers?',
    options: ['5', '8', '12', '14'],
    correctOptions: [1, 2, 3],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are prime numbers?',
    options: ['5', '8', '13', '14'],
    correctOptions: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are odd numbers?',
    options: ['5', '8', '11', '14'],
    correctOptions: [0, 2],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are divisors of 30?',
    options: ['5', '8', '11', '15'],
    correctOptions: [0, 3],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are multiples of 6?',
    options: ['6', '8', '12', '14'],
    correctOptions: [0, 2],
  },
]
